long time no see.
久しぶり
It's been a while.
久しぶりです
Bike class?
バイクラスか?
thank you.
ありがとうございます
Today, let's take care of some clothes, okay?
今日さ、ちょっと服、やろくね?
surely.
確かに
Ah, I'll come.
あー、いきますね
Was there a new store?
新店あったりした?
Haven't done it yet?
まだやってない?
Yeah.
うん
So, why did you come again?
でさ、なんでまた来てくれたの?
He contacted me.
私 に 連絡くれたんだよ
Um, I still have a disability.
あの ー、障がきがまだ
Ah, that's right.
あー、そうですね
I agree.
そうですね
Well then,
じゃあ、
Actually, I'm not at the top today.
今日 実はトップじゃないんです
A man gave it to me,
男の人がくれて、
When I showed her the photo, she thought it was really cute.
写 真見せたらさ、めっちゃ可愛いねってなって
I see.
なるほど
Well, for now, let me come in.
まあ、とりあえずは入ってきてもらおうか
please.
お願いします
Hello.
こんにちは
Wow, wow.
うわー、やば
Isn't it super cute?
超可愛いじゃないですか
Is it okay to have sex with something so cute?
こんな可愛いこと、セクスしていいんすか?
Seriously?
マジで?
That's terrible.
やばいね
Her feet are also super beautiful.
足も超綺麗だし
I mean, you can see it's so short.
だってこんな短いのもほら、見えちゃう
It's open here.
ここ開いてんだ
It's the skin.
肌だ
Oh, seriously?
え、マジで?
Great clothes.
すごい服
It seems kind of mental.
なんか、メンタルに見えちゃう
I don't look like someone should attack me.
私は襲ってくださいみたいな格好じゃないですか
That's not the case.
そんな ことないですよ
Isn't that true?
そんなことないの?
This is amazing, and it's a tight fit.
これすごい、しかもタイトな格好
Can I have you stand for a moment?
ちょっと立ってもらっていい?
That's not true.
そんなことないですよ
Best.
ベスト
Can I have you turn once?
1回転してもらっていい?
1 rotation.
1回転
It's a little embarrassing.
ちょっと恥ずかしい
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
That's also a great point.
それも盛りポイントだね
What kind of things do men do when things get a little weird?
少しやがるとね、男ってどんなことするんですよね
My ears are weak.
耳、弱いんですよ
Are you hard of hearing?
耳弱いの?
It's weak.
弱いんですよ
It's fashionable.
おしゃれだね
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
There's a bag, Maki.
袋あるね、マキに
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It tickled.
くすぐった
Maki, don't you feel good?
マキ、気持ちよくない?
Maki, it tickled me.
マキ、くすぐった
I felt better for a while.
一応気持ちよくなっちゃった
It tickled.
くすぐった
Isn't there something similar?
何か似てない?
What is this?
これ何でしょう?
what?
何?
Don't you understand?
分かんない?
It's here, it's here.
ここだよ、ここ
They look so similar.
すげえ似てるじゃん
It might be similar.
似てるかも
Is there a place that feels good?
気持ちいいところってある?
Where does it feel good?
気持ちいいところ?
Where is it?
どこだろう?
Where does it feel good?
気持ちいいところ?
Where is it being touched now?
今触られてるところは?
Feels good.
気持ちいい
I wish you could tell me.
教えてくれたらいいのに
Because everything feels good.
全部気持ちいいから
Everything feels good.
全部気持ちいい
Will it stop if I do it like this?
こうやってやったらしなくなる?
do not.
しない
The length of your hair hides it really well.
髪の長さって、すごい隠れるよ
surely.
確かに
I'm catching it when it's being licked.
なめられてるところ、つかみてるね
different.
違う
All at once.
一気に
Because I'm only looking at your butthole.
お尻の穴だけ見てるから
I showed my butt a little.
ちょっと、お尻つけ出してもった
I have a mole.
ほくろある
I have a mole in my butt hole.
お尻の穴にほくろあるよ
No way.
やだ
You didn't know this.
これ知らなかったでしょ
I can't see it myself.
自分で見れないもんね
Okay, really.
いいよ、すごく
Charming.
魅力的
Charm point.
チャームポイント
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Good, you discovered it.
よかったね、発見したね
You're probably wondering what I'm doing now.
今何してるんだろうって思ってるでしょ
I'm looking at cancer.
ガン見してんな
You're calm.
冷静だな
Look this way.
こっち向いて
Because it's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいから
Yeah, it's open.
そうそう、開いてそう
There's no way you can't see it.
見られないもんないでしょ
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Awesome.
すげー
Push it open.
押し開けるって
here we go.
さ あ
child
こ
Hey, look this way.
っち、 こっち向いて
Because that's it.
そっちだから
Try it.
やってみて
It's different on the right and left.
右と左に違うんだね
Peek from below.
下から覗いて
appear?
見える?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Push it open.
押し開けて
hand,
手、
Hand, hand.
手、 手